Guide to the Montana Attorney General's Office Records 1893-1969
Montana Historical Society Archives
- Dockets (correspondence and other material re cases)
  - Docket #7, case #276: Montana ex rel. Daniel Nice vs. State Board of Land Commissioners (re sale of land in Stillwater County), 1949 (Box-folder 102 / 16)
  - Docket #7, case #285: United States vs. 909.13 acres in Lewis and Clark County (re condemnation of land for Canyon Ferry Reservoir), 1949 (Box-folder 102 / 17)
  - Docket #7, case #288: Harry Shaw vs. Montana (re Alvin Noble Estate, Virginia City), 1949 (Box-folder 102 / 18)
  - Docket #7, case #289: Vincent Ward vs. Montana (re easement for irrigation ditch in Teton County), 1949-1950 (Box-folder 102 / 19)
  - Docket #7, case #297: E.W. Thomas vs. State Board of Examiners (re validity of University bond issue), 1949 (Box-folder 102 / 20)
  - Docket #7, case #300: Circle Farmers Club vs. Arnold Olsen, Attorney General (re gambling slot machines), 1949 (Box-folder 102 / 21)
  - Docket #7, case #303: Jeffries Coal Company vs. Industrial Accident Board, 1951-1953 (Box-folder 102 / 22)
  - Docket #7, case #307: Montana ex rel. Arnold Olsen, Attorney General vs. Louis Saginaw et al (re gambling in Helena), 1949-1950 (Box-folder 102 / 23)
  - Docket #7, case #308: Montana ex rel. Arnold Olsen, Attorney General vs. Emil Christianson (re gambling in Culberton), 1949-1950 (Box-folder 102 / 24)
  - Docket #7, case #331: Montana ex rel. Ralph J. Studer vs. State Board of Examiners (re paving at Montana State College), 1949 (Box-folder 102 / 25)
  - Docket #7, case #344: Vujo Repac vs. Industrial Accident Board (re injury claim), 1950-1953 (Box-folder 102 / 26)
  - Docket #7, case #350: R.H. fletcher, Outdoor Advertising Association vs. Montana Liquor Control Board (re ban on liquor advertising), 1949 (Box-folder 102 / 27)
  - Docket #7, case #355: Montana ex rel. Prairie County vs. Buffalo Rapids Club (re gambling slot machines), 1949-1950 (Box-folder 102 / 28)
  - Docket #7, case #356: Montana ex rel. Arnold Olsen, Attorney General vs. 30 Club (re Butte gambling), 1950 (Box-folder 102 / 29)
  - Docket #7, case #361: Montana ex rel. Lyman Bennett vs John W. Bonner (re judge disqualifications), 1949 (Box-folder 102 / 30)
  - Docket #7, case #363, 434: Montana vs. John Loy Storm (re Rosebud County murder), 1949-1951 (Box-folder 102 / 31)
  - Docket #7, case #368: W.C. Brown vs. State Dept. of Agriculture (re Dairy Queen and definition of ice cream), 1950-1952 (Box-folder 102 / 32)
  - Docket #7, case #373: Harold Bitterman vs. State Highway Commission (re damages for Lincoln County stream diversion), 1950 (Box-folder 102 / 33)
  - Docket #7, case #380: United States vs. Montana (re condemnation for expansion of Red Rock Lakes Migratory Bird Refuge), 1943-1950 (Box-folder 102 / 34)
  - Docket #7, case #386: Montana ex rel. Arnold Olsen, Attorney General vs. A.J. Darrah (re Butte gambling), 1950 (Box-folder 102 / 35)
  - Docket #7, case #390: State Water Conservation Board vs. Robert B. Fraser (re Flatwillow & Petrolia Bench projects), 1950 (Box-folder 102 / 36)
  - Docket #7, case #408: Montana vs. John coloff (re rape in Shelby), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 37)
  - Docket #7, case #411: United States vs. 8.37 acres, Hill County (re condemnation of land at Fort Assiniboine), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 38)
  - Docket #7, case #414: Montana ex rel. Ernest R. McKee vs. Montana (re renewal of Toole County grazing lease), 1950 (Box-folder 102 / 39)
  - Docket #7, case #425: Paul J. Heaney Sr. vs. Manganese Products Inc. (re Granite County phosphate lease), 1950-1951 (Box-folder 102 / 40)
  - Docket #7, case #430: Montana ex rel. Arnold Olsen, Attorney General vs. Joe Britten (re gambling at Cooke City), 1950-1951 (Box-folder 102 / 41)
  - Docket #7, case #431: Montana ex rel. Arnold Olsen, Attorney General vs. Charles J. O'Conner (re gambling at Livingston), 1949-1950 (Box-folder 102 / 42)
  - Docket #7, case #433: Montana ex rel. Arnold Olsen, Attorney General vs. J.E. "Baldy" Kelly (re gambling at Shelby), 1949-1954 (Box-folder 102 / 43)
  - Docket #7, case #435: Montana vs. Lavaun Dillon (re murder in Great Falls), 1950-1951 (Box-folder 102 / 44)
  - Docket #7, case #437: Montana vs. Andrew Pepion and Peter Tatsey (re jurisdiction in Blackfeet Indian Reservation larceny case: see also Docket 8, case 38), 1950-1951 (Box-folder 102 / 45)
  - Docket #7, case #444: J.C. Ettien vs. Stella Holt, Granite County Treasurer (re city and county taxes), 1949 (Box-folder 102 / 46)
  - Docket #7, case #458: Butte Motor Company vs. Tebb's Construction Company (re Alder Ruby Dam Project), 1950-1951 (Box-folder 102 / 47)
  - Docket #7, case #470: P.J. Kelly vs. Silver Bow County (re breach of contract), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 48)
  - Docket #7, case #474: Alexander and Hollenbeck vs. Anna flage, Rosebud County Treasurer (re taxes paid under protest), 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 49)
  - Docket #7, case #489: Montana ex rel. Elsie B. Eyman vs. State Board of Land Commissioners (re land sale in Livingston), 1951-1952 (Box-folder 102 / 50)
  - Docket #7, case #490: Lula B. Rogers Estate, Windham, 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 51)
  - Docket #7, case #491: Montana vs. Albert E. Searle (re "infamous crime against nature (homosexual)" in Lewistown), 1951-1955 (Box-folder 102 / 52)
  - Docket #7, case #500: Montana vs. Ed Pichette (re Indian hunting rights), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 54)
  - Docket #7, case #504: Montana vs. Sam Deniff et al. (re gambling in Malta), 1951-1952 (Box-folder 102 / 54)
  - Docket #7, case #505: Montana vs. Dan Jerrell and Bruce Turner (re burglary in Baker), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 55)
  - Docket #7, case #509: John C. Barnes vs. Montana (re cadastral survey on Yellowstone River), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 56)
  - Docket #7, case #515: Montana vs. William Adams (re jurisdiction in Blackfeet Indian Reservation manslaughter case), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 57)
  - Docket #7, case #517: Albert Lee Stuart Estate (bequest to Tuberculosis Sanitarium), 1953 (Box-folder 102 / 58)
  - Docket #7, case #518: Richard Meeds vs. State Board of Education (re tenure rights of Eastern Montana College math professor), 1950-1954 (Box-folder 102 / 59)
  - Docket #7, case #527: Montana vs. Bolton et al. (re condemnation for highway right of way in Silver Bow County), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 60)
  - Docket #7, case #528: In the matter of the estate of John Kennedy, an incompetent (re cost of care at Warm Springs Hospital), 1948-1951 (Box-folder 102 / 61)
  - Docket #7, case #532: Montana ex rel. James Hugh Irvine vs. District Court, Lake County (re jurisdiction on Flathead Indian Reservation), 1951-1952 (Box-folder 102 / 62)
  - Docket #7, case #535: Montana vs W.P. Bosch (re manslaughter in Yellowstone County auto accident), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 63)
  - Docket #7, case #538: H.F. Johnson Inc. et al. vs. State Board of Railroad Commissioners, 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 64)
  - Docket #7, case #539: United States vs. William H. Wallace et al. (re condemnation for transmission line, Deer Lodge County), 1951-1952 (Box-folder 102 / 65)
  - Docket #7, case #543: Montana vs. Jesse Perez (re closing time of Forsyth bar; floor plan of Century Club, Forsyth in oversize folder), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 66)
  - Docket #7, case #545: Montana vs. Raymond L. Deems (re Havre burglary), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 67)
  - Docket #7, case #546: Louis C. Aprato vs. Industrial Accident Board (re injury claim at Bearcreek coal mine), 1951-1953 (Box-folder 102 / 68)
  - Docket #7, case #547: Montana vs. Frank R. Dryman, alias Frank Valentine (re Shelby murder), 1951-1952 (Box-folder 102 / 69)
  - Docket #7, case #548: Montana vs. William Patrick Quinlan (re assault in Missoula), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 70)
  - Docket #7, case #552: Ole Hanson petition (re establishing death of Ethel L. Hanson, Missoula), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 71)
  - Docket #7, case #557: May G. Clark vs. State Board of Land Commissioners (re sale of Toole County land), 1950-1951 (Box-folder 102 / 72)
  - Docket #7, case #565: Montana vs. Clarence Nickerson (re assault involving non-Indians on Fort Belknap Indian Reservation), 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 73)
  - Docket #7, case #571: Laurence S. Carlson vs. Flathead County (re taxes paid under protest), 1952-1953 (Box-folder 102 / 74)
  - Docket #7, case #579: The Yellowstone Company vs. State Board of Pharmacy, 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 75)
  - Docket #8, case #8: Montana vs. Edmund G. Toomey (re recovery of income taxes), 1953 (Box-folder 102 / 76)
  - Docket #8, case #11: Montana vs. Joseph Henry Keller and Lee Piveral (re fraud by false weights at truck scales), 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 77)
  - Docket #8, case #16: William J. Wheeler vs. State Board of Land Commissioners), 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 78)
  - Docket #8, case #17: R.E. Davis vs. State Board of Land Commissioners (re sale of Gallatin County land), 1952-1953 (Box-folder 102 / 79)
  - Docket #8, case #18: Montana vs. Calvin Simon et al. (re admission to bail on appeal), 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 80)
  - Docket #8, case #24: Montana vs. Oscar Baillargeron (re over-weight truck), 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 81)
  - Docket #8, case #34: Montana vs. King Colony Ranch (re corporation tax assessed on Hutterite farm), 1949-1952 (Box-folder 102 / 83)
  - Docket #8, case #27: Joe Spoya Estate, Missoula County, 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 84)
  - Docket #8, case #38: Montana ex rel. Peter Tatsy vs. 3rd Judicial District Court (re jurisdiction on Blackfeet Reservation; see also Docket 7 case 437), 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 84)
  - Docket #8, case #41: Montana vs. Eva Erlandson (re selling beer to minor in Havre), 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 85)
  - Docket #8, case #42: Montana vs. Evelyn Donges and Tom LaFave (re murder by 16-year olds in Miles City), 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 86)
  - Docket #8, case #51: Carpenter Paper Company vs. Minnesota and Montana Land Company (re building plans in Billings townsite), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 87)
  - Docket #8, case #63: Goerge Kustudia vs. Industrial Accident Board (re injury claim), 1952-1953 (Box-folder 102 / 88)
  - Docket #8, case #64: Montana vs. Leo Norby (re auto theft in Havre), 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 89)
  - Docket #8, case #70: S. Birch and Sons Construction Company vs. State Highway Commission (re Rogers Pass to Simms highway), 1952 (Box-folder 102 / 90)
  - Docket #8, case #83: Montana vs. John Phillips (re forgery in gas tax refund fraud case in Missoula), 1951-1953 (Box-folder 102 / 91)
  - Docket #8, case #85: Montana vs. James M. Hughes (re theft of cow in Teton County), 1952-1953 (Box-folder 102 / 92)
  - Docket #8, case #91: Frances A. Garnett vs. Idaho Compensation Company (re injury claim), 1951 (Box-folder 102 / 93)
  - Docket #8, case #105: Montana ex rel. William A. Dickgraber vs. Charles A. Sheridan, State Treasurer (re (re oil and gas leases), 1950-1953 (Box-folder 102 / 94)
  - Docket #8, case #112: Montana ex rel. Willis B. Jones vs. State Board of Land Commissioners (re oil and gas lease), 1953-1955 (Box-folder 102 / 95)
  - Docket #8, case #114: Ahmed Mohamed Abbas vs. Fatima Abbas et al. (to quiet to drafts on Butte bank), 1953 (Box-folder 102 / 96)
  - Docket #8, case #115: Montana vs. Frank R. Dryman (re murder in Shelby), 1953 (Box-folder 102 / 97)
  - Docket #8, case #125: Associated Students Store, Montana State College, Bozeman vs. Thomas M. Robinson (re tax recovery), 1953 (Box-folder 102 / 98)
  - Docket #8, case #126: Jake Jacobson vs. State Unemployment Compensation Commission (re amendments to unemployment compensation law), 1953 (Box-folder 102 / 99)
  - Docket #8, case #130: S. Birch and Sons Construction Company vs. State Highway Commission (re licensing of road construction equipment), 1953 (Box-folder 102 / 100)
  - Docket #8, case #132: Montana vs. Marvin W. McBain (re desertion of children in Ravalli County), 1953-1954 (Box-folder 102 / 101)
  - Docket #8, case #139: Montana ex rel. Arnold Olsen, Attorney General vs. Montana Armory Board (re armory building in Poplar), 1952-1956 (Box-folder 102 / 102)
  - Docket #8, case #154: Montana ex rel. Arnold Olsen, Attorney General vs. Raymond Joseph Sundling (re theft of road roller from Highway Dept.), 1953-1955 (Box-folder 102 / 103)
  - Docket #8, case #170: Montana ex rel. Arnold Olsen, Attorney General vs. Walter D. Rankin (re State Park Commission and Goose Bay State Park; includes correspondence, exhibits, Financial History of State Park Commission, reports, etc.), 1947-1955 (Box-folder 102 / 104-109)
  - Docket #8, case #175: Montana vs. William T. Reid (re rape in Blaine County), 1953-1954 (Box-folder 102 / 110)
  - Docket #8, case #177: Montana vs. John Kendrick (re assault in Carter County), 1953 (Box-folder 102 / 111)
  - Docket #8, case #194: Treasure County vs. Mountain States Clay Products (re bentonite mining lease), 1953 (Box-folder 102 / 112)
  - Docket #8, case #205: United States vs. 129.8 acres Broadwater County (re condemnation for Crow Creek Unit), 1954 (Box-folder 102 / 113)
  - Docket #8, case #207: Montana vs. A.F. Allen (re confidence game in Great Falls), 1954 (Box-folder 102 / 114)
  - Docket #8, case #224: Angus McDonald Jr. et al. vs. N.T. McIntosh, Sanders County assessor (re confederated Salish and Kootenai Indian tribes), 1954-1955 (Box-folder 102 / 115)
  - Docket #8, case #251: Montana vs. John Loy Storm (re Rosebud County murder; see also Docket 7, cases 363, 434), 1952-1954 (Box-folder 102 / 116)
  - Docket #8, case #252: Montana ex rel. William L. Bokas vs. District Court, Roosevelt County (re jurisdiction on Fort Peck Indian Reservation), 1954 (Box-folder 102 / 117)
  - Docket #8, case #254: Harsh Montana Corporation vs. Cascade County (re taxation of property on Malmstrom Air Base), 1955 (Box-folder 102 / 118)
  - Docket #8, case #257: Montana vs. State Public Service Commission (re Montana-Dakota Utilities Company), 1955 (Box-folder 102 / 119)
  - Docket #8, case #258: Montana vs. State Public Service Commission and Montana Power Company (re Montana Power Company rates, natural gas prices, and sale of timber on state land in Glacier Park), 1954-1956 (Box-folder 102 / 120)
  - Docket #8, case #264: Montana ex rel. Wright Haggerty vs. State Liquor Control Board (re liquor license application, Blackfeet Indian Tribe intervenors), 1954 (Box-folder 102 / 121)
  - Docket #8, case #288: Josephine Cannon Estate, Billings (re bequest to Roman Catholic Church of the Little Flower), 1953 (Box-folder 102 / 122)
  - Docket #8, case #304: James C. Cory and Winifred Cory vs. Margaret B. Kemp et al. (to quiet title on Custer County land), 1954 (Box-folder 102 / 123)
  - Docket #8, case #311: Montana vs. Lewis Parr (re selling liquor to minor in Lewistown), 1954-1955 (Box-folder 102 / 124)
  - Docket #8, case #322, 324: Montana ex rel. School districts 20 & 28, Hill County vs. State Board of Education (re funds for non-accredited schools), 1954-1955 (Box-folder 102 / 125)
  - Docket #8, case #336: Montana ex rel. Robert F. Hardy vs. State Board of Equalization (re taxation), 1955 (Box-folder 102 / 126)
  - Docket #8, case #358: Montana ex rel. V.G. Koch, Richland County Attorney vs. John M. Lexcen (re county attorney contest), 1954-1955 (Box-folder 102 / 127)
  - Docket #8, case #363: Gardner C. Waite vs. John J. Holmes, State Auditor (re Saskatchewan Guarantee and Fidelity Company, Ltd., Canada), 1954-1957 (Box-folder 102 / 128)
  - Docket #8, case #365: Mariam C. Bunker vs. Montana (to quiet title on Gallatin County land), 1955 (Box-folder 102 / 129)
  - Docket #8, case #370: Montana, ex rel. Aronold Olsen, Attorney General vs. Robert F. Swanberg and harold L. McChesney (re chairmanship of Industrial Accident Board), 1955 (Box-folder 102 / 130)
  - Docket #8, case #392: Montana vs. Alan R. Bain (re practice of medicine without license in Great Falls), 1955 (Box-folder 102 / 131)
  - Docket #8, case #395: Daisy M. Langman vs. Mary E. whittelsey (re mineral rights on Messelshell County land), 1955 (Box-folder 102 / 132)
  - Docket #8, case #396: Montana ex rel. John V. Schara vs. John J. Holmes, State Auditor (re constitutionality of bill creating Montana Legislative Council), 1955 (Box-folder 102 / 133)
  - Docket #8, case #406: J.J. Schladweiller et al. vs. State Board of Equalization (re duties of Board), 1956 (Box-folder 103 / 1)
  - Docket #8, case #414: Montana vs. Lewis Gates (re cattle theft in Golden Valley County), 1956-1957 (Box-folder 103 / 2)
  - Docket #8, case #424: Montana vs. Antonio Gascar (re grand larceny in Billings), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 103 / 3)
  - Docket #8, case #428: Montana vs. W.D. Widdecombe (re illegal possession of fur-bearing animal in Sweet Grass County), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 103 / 4)
  - Docket #8, case #443: Katie Davis vs. Yellowstone County (re naturalization fees), 1956 (Box-folder 103 / 5)
  - Docket #8, case #446: Montana vs. Emil Paskvan (re sale of liquor to minor in Three Forks), 1957 (Box-folder 103 / 6)
  - Docket #8, case #452: Montana vs. Raymond L. Deeds (re exclusion of Indians from Hill County jury lists), 1956-1957 (Box-folder 103 / 7)
  - Docket #8, case #458: Montana vs. Wiley F. Blakeslee (re rape in Powell County), 1957 (Box-folder 103 / 8)
  - Docket #8, case #459: Montana vs. Lawrence R. Morran (re murder in Phillips County), 1957 (Box-folder 103 / 9)
  - Docket #8, case #463: Montana vs. Marvin Cockrell (re assault in Galata), 1957 (Box-folder 103 / 10)
  - Docket #8, case #500: C.R. Miller and H. Duane Simmons vs. Cut Bank High School District (re construction of gymnasium), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 103 / 11)
  - Docket #8, case #517: Montana vs. E.T. Ganger (re "infamous crime against nature" (homosexual) by Lewistown doctor), 1955-1956 (Box-folder 103 / 12)
  - Docket #8, case #532: Juanita B. Elliott vs. State Highway Commission (re Yellow Bay State Park and Montana State University Biological Station), 1956-1957 (Box-folder 103 / 13)
  - Docket #8, case #536: Central Surety and Insurance Company vs. John J. Holmes, State Auditor (re administration building at State Industrial School for Boys, Miles City), 1955 (Box-folder 103 / 14)
  - Docket #8, case #545: Montana vs. Duane Alexander (re assault in Teton County), 1957 (Box-folder 103 / 15)
  - Docket #8, case #546: Montana vs. James Rother Jr. (re perjury in gas tax refund fraud case), 1952-1956 (Box-folder 103 / 16)
  - Docket #8, case #550: Montana vs. Robert D. MacLean and George Bukovatz (re false claim for sheriff's fees in Missoula County), 1954 (Box-folder 103 / 17)
  - Docket #8, case #556: Montana vs. William Nicks (re "lewd and lascivious acts on minor" in Miles City), 1956-1958 (Box-folder 103 / 18)
  - Docket #8, case #558: Montana ex rel. J.L. Yuhas, M.D. vs. Board of Medical Examiners (re malpractice including performing abortions, using syphilis-infected blood, performing unnecessary operations etc. in Missoula), 1956-1957 (Box-folder 103 / 19)
  - Docket #8, case #561: Montana ex rel. Frank Bajt vs. State Unemployment Compensation Commission (re labor strike at Roundup), 1956 (Box-folder 103 / 20)
  - Docket #8, case #578: State Highway Commission vs. J. Bruce Orcott (re route of planned interstate highway in Custer County), 1957 (Box-folder 103 / 21)
  - Docket #8, case #579: George F. Crosby vs. Montana (re oil and gas reservation in sale of state land in Big Horn County), 1956 (Box-folder 103 / 22)
  - Docket #8, case #583: Montana ex rel. State Oil and Gas Commission vs. Doral Pilling and Western Surety Company (re unplugged oil well), 1956 (Box-folder 103 / 23)
  - Docket #9, case #2: Charles W. Grupe Estate (re bequest to School of Mines for Frank Little Memorial), 1954-1956 (Box-folder 103 / 24)
  - Docket #9, case #4: Ruth Colgrove Ulmer vs. Maggie Elliot vs. Montana (re oil, gas and mineral rights on highway right of way), 1957 (Box-folder 103 / 25)
  - Docket #9, case #16: Halvor Linden and Lawrence H. Linden vs. Montana (to quiet title to Flathead County property), 1957 (Box-folder 103 / 26)
  - Docket #9, case #46: Montana ex rel. Donald Allen vs. State Board of Education (re bids for construction of buildings at Western Montana College, Dillon), 1957 (Box-folder 103 / 27)
  - Docket #9, case #90: Montana vs. William J. Nelson (re burglary in Yellowstone County), 1957-1962 (Box-folder 103 / 28)
  - Docket #9, case #114: James Heimbichner vs. Montana Milk Control Board (re interpretation of Milk Control Act), 1957 (Box-folder 103 / 29)
  - Docket #9, case #122: Montana ex rel. Carl Geschwender vs. Mark La Rowe, Justice of Peace (re liquor license in McCone County), 1957 (Box-folder 103 / 30)
  - Docket #9, case #194, 195: Montana ex rel. Vita-Rich Dairy, Inc. vs. Montana Milk Control Board (re Hill and Roosevelt County cases), 1958 (Box-folder 103 / 31)
  - Docket #9, case #246, 247, 248: Montana vs. Vernon Dumont; Montana vs. Richard Wilson; Montana vs. Leslie P. Shields (re Indian jurisdiction in Wolf Point), 1959 (Box-folder 103 / 32)
  - Docket #9, case #258: city of Fort Benton vs. State Board of Health (re sewer lines), 1959 (Box-folder 103 / 33)
  - Docket #9, case #260: Dan W. Lynch and Florence W. Lynch vs. Montana (to quiet title on Flathead County property), 1959 (Box-folder 103 / 34)
  - Docket #9, case #268: Patrick Brandenburg vs. William A. Halberg and Montana (re damages for auto accident), 1959 (Box-folder 103 / 35)
  - Docket #9, case #286: Montana vs. Clarence Kanada Brown (re check forgery in Great Falls), 1959 (Box-folder 103 / 36)
  - Docket #9, case #288: United States vs. 16.17 acres (re condemnation for water pipelines to Glasgow Air Base), 1959 (Box-folder 103 / 37)
  - Docket #9, case #299: State Forester vs. Whitefish Lumber Company (re slash disposal payments), 1958-1960 (Box-folder 103 / 38)
  - Docket #9, case #348: Montana vs. Robert R. Peterson and Mary D. Peterson (re milk control in Missoula County), 1959 (Box-folder 103 / 39)
  - Docket #9, case #355: Andrew W. Palo vs. Yellowstone County Commissioners (re county attorney salary), 1957-1960 (Box-folder 103 / 40)
  - Docket #9, case #361: Montana vs. Warren William Hollywood (re lie detector use in Gallatin County murder case), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 103 / 41)
  - Docket #9, case #362: Wiley Blakeslee vs. Montana (re habeas corpus in rape conviction), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 103 / 42)
  - Docket #9, case #365: Murphy Corporation vs. Montana (re State Oil and Gas Conservation Commission), 1960 (Box-folder 103 / 43)
  - Docket #9, case #409: Montana ex rel. Neil C. Livingston vs. Frank Murray, Secretary of State (re distribution of proposed constitutional amendment), 1960 (Box-folder 103 / 44)
  - Docket #9, case #438: LeRoy H. Jones vs. Montana (re writ of certiorari in Glasgow grand larceny case), 1960 (Box-folder 103 / 45)
  - Docket #9, case #458: United States vs. 857.10 acres, Beaverhead County (re condemnation for Clark Canyon Dam), 1960 (Box-folder 103 / 46)
  - Docket #9, case #470: United States vs. 12.15 acres, Lewis and Clark County (re condemnation for missile silo site), 1960-1961 (Box-folder 103 / 47)
  - Docket #9, case #472: Montana vs. Wayne C. Gilbert (re driving under influence of liquor), 1960 (Box-folder 103 / 48)
  - Docket #9, case #506: Montana vs. Larry Allmaras (re use of liquor by minor in Shelby), 1960 (Box-folder 103 / 49)
  - Docket #9, case #516: Montana vs. Charles Fairbanks (re credit for time served on previous conviction), 1962 (Box-folder 103 / 50)
  - Docket #9, case #541: Montana vs. Gene Stanley Davis (re liquor sales to minors in Libby), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 103 / 51)
  - Docket #9, case #559: Gertrude McStravick vs. Russell Manger (re lease of state land in Meagher County), 1961 (Box-folder 103 / 52)
  - Docket #9, case #571: In the matter of W.D. Hirst (re disbarment), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 103 / 53)
  - Docket #9, case #576: Montana vs. Ralph Moore (re practicing medicine without license in Malta), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 103 / 54)